̾߱.
Previously on Weeds.
¥ ұ غôµ.
I've been giving some thoughts to my cover business.
Ŀ ?
What do you think about a bakery?
̰ е ⵵ äְ
These will satisfy your munchies
ִ°.
and give you a long lasting, all body high.
. ֹްڽϴ.
I'm ready to take orders.
! .
Fuck it! I'll take it all.
, ̹ , , .
Last week's buy, this week's buy, my ring, my Rover.
̹ ֿ ٴ° ڶ.
You're still short for all the shit you're gonna wanna take this week.
ݹ ã ò.
I'll be back.
I don't like dealing with things.
ذϴ ʾ.
׳ ô ϴ° .
I much prefer to pretend they don't exist.
ް!
Megan!
, ް!
Hey, Megan!
ް! 鸮?
Megan! Can you hear me?
̰ ͸ӰŸھ.
That deaf girl down on Dewey Street.
̾! !
Fire! Fire!
, ؿ? ҳݾƿ!
Mom, what are you doing? There's a fire!
׶ ۰. ˾?
If there's a fire, I'll run. Okay?
ƴϸ, ڷ Ⱘ⸦ εָ ǰ.
Otherwise I'm gonna bash in the smoke alarm with the broom handle.
ص?
Andy?
̾, , ٶ ׷µ.
Sorry, Pants, I was trying to surprise you guys.
Uncle Andy!
ص !
!
Hey!
׷, ±!
Yes, I'm digging the love!
;!
I missed you!
˷ī ?
So how was Alaska?
Ƹٿ.
Alaska was so beautiful.
ö, Ƽ .
In the summer, you can party all night.
׸ οµ ģڸ µ
ڲ ҷ ϴ.
Then it got dark and I met this psycho girl who tried to bring me up on charges.
 Ծ?
How did you get in here?
â , ͼ!
I'll swear I'll pay for the window.
Ⱦٰ.
I didn't wanna wake you.
̾! , .
I'm joking! I'm joking! I'm joking!
ħ ° Ͷ.
You guys wanna help me make breakfast?
϶, ֽ .
Silas, I need you squeezing the oranges.
Shane, I need you making the coffee.
Ŀ .
⸧ ¿ ̾.
Sorry about the grease fire.
⸧.
That bacon really spits up.
Shane, go get a broom so I can bash your uncle Andy with it.
, ְ ڷ Ͷ.
̺, ! ٻ 丮 ִٰ!
Come on, Nancy Pantsy! I'm making eggs Florentine.
θ.
׷ Ÿ̶ ҷ?
̷ , ?
Oh shit, you?
Ÿ!
Hey, Lupita!
׸? ̶?
I know you missed me. How about a hug?
I'm no cleaning up his mess.
ΰ ġ!
ص , ?
Uncle Andy, did you bring us anything?
Of course!
翬 !
.
Look who you're talking to.
Go get my duffle in the guest room, the black one.
մԹ濡 ͺ, .
Not the green, okay? Stay out of the green.
׳ɵΰ, ˾? յ .
մԹ, մԹ?
Guest room? Guest room?
Ÿϰ ־.
I guess I could sleep with Lupita.
ƾڸ ݾ.
I do love the fiery latinas.
Ÿ, ߾˾Ƶֿ.
Know this, Lupita,
ϰ ɶ,
until you learn to love me,
츮 λ ŭ ϰ .
I've got enough love for both of us.
װ ִٿ ӿ Դٴ° ȹϰ.
How did you and Judah emerge from the same woman?
˾.
I know.
What family gets blessed with not one but two studs?
ڰ ϳ ƴϰ Ѿ̳ ູ .
Okay, everybody gather.
, ̼.
,
First,
϶,
young Silas,
޾ƶ.
that is for you.
̳.
Awesome.
̰ Ǵ°?
So, does it work?
Yeah, for about another 3 weeks,
׷, 3 ɲ,
Ŀ øѹ .
then you're gonna wanna scratch off the serial number and get a new service plan.
, .
Okay, for mamma,
What's that?
װ ?
For your neck, right?
ȸϴ°ž.
You're always talking about how your neck hurts.
׻ ٰ ׷ݾ.
- Andy, this is...
- Take it.
- ص, ̰...
- ޾.
ȸ, ¾.
For my neck, of course.
. Ÿ.
Thank you. Lupita.
ħǿ , .
I'll put it in your bedroom, next to the little one.
¿!
What about me?
Oh... I don't...
... װ ...
!
Oh!
ְ !
Best for last!
!
No way!
No! No way !
ȵ, ȵ!
 ϴ° ġ ݾ.
Come on, I'll teach him how to use it.
, ̸.
Shane Li, hand it over.
ص!
Andy!
Ҷ .
I'll hold on to those 'till we're in a better space.
Who's hungry?
»?
ε, !
Everybody, go sit down!
ص...
Andy...
󸶳 ?
how long are you planning on staying?
, ϵ ŵ鲲.
Don't worry, I'll help out.
󸶳?
How long?
˾Ƴ.
Just 'till I figure some things out.
?
Like?
۽.
I don't know.
λ.
My life.
׷?
Sure.
¥?
That.
Good to see you, Pants.
󱼺ϱ , .
It's good to be a family.
̶ ž.
Come on, let's eat!
, ħڰ!
!, ϰ ֳ?
Hey, buddy! What are you doing?
ģ ޽ ϰ ־.
Just IMing my girlfriend.
װ ϴ° ƴ?
You don't need a credit card for that, do you?
ƴϾ.
No.
Real girlfriend. Megan. She's deaf.
¥ ģ. ް̶ ͸ӰŸ.
͸ӰŸ ް̶. ?
Deaf Megan. She cute?
׷, ̻.
Yeah, she's totally cute.
̾!
Yeah.
͸ӰŸó Ⱥ̴µ.
She doesn't look deaf.
׷ ƹ͵ ȵ鸮°ž?
She can't hear anything?
That's what deaf means.
'͸ӰŸ' װ Ƹ?
, ׷ ȶϳ, ?
Man, how did you get so smart at what? 16?
¦ ұ ֵ ô° µ ɷȾµ.
Took me years to learn slightly defective chicks are the way to go.
I once went out with this chick with a baby arm:
ѹ ڶ ϰ ־.
ħ뿡 .
insane in the sack.
Plus, when she grabbed my dick with her little hand, it looked gigantic.
Դٰ, ְ ڶ ȷ , װ û Ŀ.
So how you talk to her?
ȭ  ϳ?
׳ ϰ ׷ .
We just mostly hang out and stuff.
'' ͵ ߰ڴ.
You should learn Braille.
You mean sign language?
'ȭ'.
Whatever.
Ͽ.
̰ ?
What's this?
.
That's mine.
Chris died for your sins!
ũ ˸ ׾ϴ.
Is that a joke?
̾?
׷, ѽ.
Yeah, on me.
ƿ ٴϱ.
That's what happens when you outsource to fucking Malaysia.
忡 ¥ öڹ ˰ڳ.
8-year-olds in a sweatshop can't spell for shit.
ȭ ̵ ӿ  ߾.
See, I was trying to jump on board the whole red state Jesus thing.
The Fashion of the Christ.
' м'̶.
ᱹ ̰ õ常 Ȱ .
I end up with 3000 of these.
ƹ¦ ̵ ̾.
Totally useless.
ȸ ٴϴ 鿡 ؼ Ȯ ϳ ִµ,
Because if there's one thing I learned about the Christ crowd,
гŭ ٴ ž.
absolutely no sense of humor.
ε ٳ ϴ°ǵ.
Should have gone after the jew market.
At least we can take a joke.
׷ ̶ ְ ޾ٵ.
, .
Come on, Shane.
Գ .
Look who's here.
̺, Ͼ °ž.
Baby, it's "the early bird gets the worm".
ȭ ƴϰ.
Not the weed.
Ӵ о.
Need to read up on your Bartlett's.
ֵ ֵ б ŵ.
My brother-in-law took the kids to school.
׷ Ϸ縦 .
I thought I'd get a jump on the day.
Want some oatmeal?
Ʈ ?
ƴ, ص 丮 ŵ.
No, Andy made eggs Florentine.
Andy?
ص?
When that fancy cooking trouble get back in town?
ĩ 丮 ƿԾ?
This morning.
ħ.
Ͼ ϱ ִ.
I woke up and there he was.
̾, ġᰡ ȵż Ż, ȱ׷?
Sort of like crotch crabs, only not as treatable, huh?
I forgot you know him.
ص ˰ִٴ° Ծ.
Ծ ڳ.
I've been hoping to forget him.
صϰ ܷ  ž?
How did Andy and Conrad meet?
Ѵ ⸦ ִ.
I never got a straight answer out of either of them.
Կ ߾µ.
They worked at circuit city together.
ĳٰ ɸ.
Got caught stealing together.
©.
Got fired together.
.
They go way back.
׷ ΰ Ҿߵ.
Never should've let that boy work retail.
׷ ߿ ٽ ;߰ڴµ.
You're gonna need to come back later
ֹ غ ȵƾ.
'cause we ain't got in everything you ordered yet.
ֹ 17̳ зȴµ.
I've got 17 food orders to fill.
丮 䳻° !
Listen to Betty Cracker.
ݾ.
You got bunches of that crap last time.
?
You're out already?
ֱ ѵ ֹ ä ڶ.
I've got some but not enough for what I need to make.
ǿ⺸ Դ° .
My crowd loves to eat their smoke.
I could hook you up with a little schwag if you're really crazy.
ȵǰ ٸ ϰ ְ.
̷ !
Oh shit!
I still have the gourmet fuck up in my kitchen.
ξ ħ Ծ õ.
ֹ̰ ƹ͵ ϰڳ.
I'm never gonna get anything done.
!
Oh fuck!
I'm fucked!
̸ °!
You got a nasty mouth when you stress.
Ʈ ĥ° ˾?
־?
You've got a pen?
ȣ ״ϱ.
I'ma give you a number.
ȭϷٰ ϸ .
And you say I said it is okay for you to call.
Who am I calling?
?
The Candyman.
ĵ.
ȭ Ű .
Wear sporty shoes.
Megan89: Are you home?
ް89: ִ?
׷.
Yeah.
. ļ.
Me too. Sore throat.
Bummer.
ȵƴ.
԰ ־?
What are you wearing?
.
Take it off.
Okay.
׷.
ҹ ߴٰ.
I tried to spread the word.
, ʴϰ.
I ate here everyday, invited people.
"Ը ȸ¾ƿ!"
"It's too ethnic!"
"ʹ ſ!"
"It's too spicy!"
" յ ȾĴ´!"
"Those people don't wash their hands!"
ø ΰ ϴ Ĵ翡
What the fuck is wrong with these morons who go to
ѽð ټ ٸ
wait an hour in line in some
û ͵ ظ ϰھ.
fucking crappy Olive Garden
̷ Ĵ մ  ع ̾.
and let a treasure like this go out of business?
ذ ȵ.
I can't take it.
, °ž?
Doug, why are we here?
Did you taste the Saag Alu?
˷ Ծþ?
̸Դ ϳ ׾ .
It's to die for.
And then be reincarnated and to die for again.
׾ٰ ٽ Ƴ Դٰ ׾ 𸥴ٱ.
ȸԾ?
Why aren't you eating?
Ծٰ ݾ.
I told you I ate already.
?
Where?
The Olive Garden.
ø 翡.
ø ܵ ȴ.
I wouldn't take a dump in the Olive Garden.
I like the hot artichoke spinach dip.
ű Դ ſ ñġ Ƽo .
I can't even look at you.
ڱ Ĵٺ .
, ׸, ׸!
Okay, enough! Enough!
и ˷簡 ϱ ׷.
I'm sure the Saag Alu is delicious.
, ε.
Well, that's incredible.
̰ Դ .. ξ ?
Tell me this doesn't kick artichoke dip's ass!
.
Tell me more.
? !
Are your nipples hard? Come on!
˺ ó. .
Like shooting stars. Now you.
ƴ, غ. ִ?
No, more of you. Are you touching yourself?
ȫ Ⱦ.
I'm parting the lips of my blushing vagina.
׷! .
Yes! Good.
ĺ!
Keep typing!
⸦ Ŀ ٲٸ  ?
What do you think about this place as the bakery?
I mean, location is pretty good.
׷ϱ, ġ .
Kitchen's already set up.
ξ ̹ ٸ ְ.
׳ ͵ 밭 ġ ,
If you make something mediocre enough,
You may even make a go at it.
װɷε ݾ.
Legitimately.
չ ̾.
Let me think about it.
غڰ.
ֽϴ, .
Here you go, Mr. Wilson.
20 orders for you.
ֹϽ 20 Դϴ.
ֱ ִ° ð.
Remember to let them cool before you put them in the freezer.
ٴϾ, Ҳ?
Mr. Bani, where will you go?
ó ø  .
We just bought in a Olive Garden franchise close by.
ѹ 鸣.
You must come visit.
Ծ! ׷ƽ
Fuck Agrestic!
¾ƿ.
Yes, sir.
.
Okay.
غǸ ϼ.
Pay when you're ready.
Ǵ°ž?
When are my treats coming in?
I'm having a little trouble
ξ µ ణ
־ ̾.
getting my kitchen to myself lately but
غǸ ˷ٲ.
I'll let you know.
Ÿ. ϰ ־.
Hey, Lupita. I was just thinking about you.
It's for you.
ã.
Wipe your hands.
۰.
Yeah, this is Andy.
ص ȭ ٲϴ.
Hey, Shane!
!
?
Really?
Ҿ!
Awesome!
׷, .
Yeah, I'll bring the shirts.
15 ɸž.
Let's say 15 minutes.
˾Ҿ...
Okay...
20 .
Make it 20.
Okay.
.
! "ũ ״" Ƽ Դϴ. ̸ !
Get your original "Chris died" t-shirts. Right here! Yeah!
Only 10 dollars! Have your money ready!
10޷ۿ մϴ! غϼ!
Here you go!
It's one size fits all. It's gonna shrink a little bit.
ѻ ´´ܴ. ߿ پ ž.
!
Oh yeah!
, ̰ ײ.
Okay, that's for you.
ص .
Uncle Andy.
, , ? .
What? What? What? Hang on.
ص !
Uncle Andy!
, , ũ ʸ Ѵܴ.
Now remember, kids, Chris loves you.
- ص !
- ֱ׷?
- Uncle Andy!
- What?
弱 Ϳ.
It's the principal.
̷ , ȸѵ.
Oh shit, man! We were just heating up.
Ƿմϴ.
Excuse me.
, , ũ 󰣴.
Look, kids, Chris has risen.
ٷ!
Wait!
ūϳ.
Oh no!
Have you all seen these?
ε ̰ ̾?
б Ⱦ!
They're all over the school!
⵶μ,
And as a christian, I must say
ȭ׿. ̰ ż̿.
I am deeply, deeply offended. It's profane.
弱Կ Ͻ ?
Has anyone talked to the principal about this?
ũ ?
Who's Chris?
Ǹƴ ?
Where's Celia?
ǸƵ ؼ Ҹ ſ.
I bet she'd have something to say.
It's 10 minutes after, maybe we should start without her.
10̳ , ׳ Ǹ .
ȸ ˾ƿ?
Does anyone know how?
Well, I think we need to
׳ ϴ° ڳ׿.
ù° Ȱ ǾѴٰ ؿ.
and I think the first order of business should be these shirts.
װ ڴ°ݾƿ.
They're funny.
Excuse me?
?
ũ ƿ. 峭ݾƿ.
I think you're making way too big a deal about it. It's a joke.
츰 ִ ũ̽Ʈ ؼ ʾƿ.
We do not joke about our Lord, Jesus Christ.
It's a stupid t-shirt.
׳ Ƽ ݾƿ.
We should ignore it.
ôϰ ѾѴٰ.
Ѻ ˸ ׾,
̸ ũ ƴϿ.
Only one man died for my sins, Nancy, and his name wasn't Chris.
۽,  ũ ƿ.
ó .
Well, it sort of was, wasn't it? Like a nickname?
츮 ũ , ȿ
б ϰ ȴٰ.
If we make a big deal about it, in a week, it will become a full-blown trend.
They're kids, it will become cool.
̶ֵ, ׳ ֵ ȴٰ.
弱! Ұ潺 ̾?
Principal Dodge! Have you seen these blasphemes?
Yes, Maggie, I have.
׷, ű, þ.
ġ Ͻ ?
Are you gonna do something about them?
I'm about to.
׷.
Ʈ , 繫Ƿ ðھ?
Mrs. Botwin, would you mind coming into my office
Ƶ Ƽ ؼ Ұ ֽϴ.
to discuss your son's little t-shirt business?
װ ȾҾ?
Shane was selling them?
׷ϴ.
Yes.
 ϰ ̿.
With some guy in a van who sped off.
ſ.
I'll never talk.
Ծ?
Hey!
 .
What do you like better?
"Jesus say relax"
" ض ϼ̴."
ƴϸ " 츮ִԲ ʹ "
or "I'm too sexy for my Lord"?
̰  "¥ ڽ"
How about "Asshole ditched my 10-year-old".
˾. ʹ Ȳߴٰ. ȣ⸦ Ҵϱ.
I admit it. I panicked. That guy had a whistle!
дϰ .
They wanted to suspend him.
˸?
For what?
If Shane wants to believe in Chris
ũ ϱ ߰
װͶ Ѵٸ...
and they try to suspend him for it...
! װ !
Wow! That's freedom of religion!
װ 10 1 Ŷ.
That's like the first commandment.
We can nail them on that.
׷ɷ ų .
'ũ' ִ° ƴѰ , ص.
I don't think Chris is protected under freedom of religion, Andy.
In fact, the angry christian moms
, кθ ӿ
I heard from in the PTA were pretty offended by it.
ũ 'ũ' ȭ ٰ.
۽, װ ޾Ƶ .
Well, that's so intolerant.
, ̶  ?
I mean, what would Jesus do?
ȵǴ ġ, 󸶳
Religious bullshit aside, you don't wanna know
how far I had to crawl up the principal's ass
弱 Ͻ
just to keep you two out of trouble.
Ƹ Ұž.
ôϴ ũ ͵ ܼҸ
Not to mention, the unbelievable amount of shit I'm gonna get from those
󸶳 Ƴİ.
hypochristian bitch moms tomorrow.
I was just trying to pitch in,
׳ ȿ Ƿ ׷ٰ.
 ̾.
earn a little money.
ȸ ԰,
I saw an opportunity to help the family and
ȸ Ŷ.
I took it.
¥?
Really?
ѰŶ, ?
It was for the family, huh?
?
Where's the money?
, ؼ ״ϱ.
Don't worry, I'll use it towards family expenses.
?
Hello?
I gotta cover my other expenses.
ٸ ȴµ.
Yeah, I did call.
, ȭ߾.
ȭּż ׿.
Thanks for getting back to me.
ٷ ֽðھ?
Can you hold on a second, please?
ٸΰ, ȭ ޾ƾ .
Go away, I have to take this call.
Who is it?
?
Ű澲 ٸ ϱ.
None of your business. Get out of here.
? ģ?
Why? You got a boyfriend?
̸ ƴϾ? ̺극 ߰ڴµ.
Isn't it a little soon? Maybe I should take my vibrator back.
Fine, Angry!
˾Ҿ! ׸!
Ȼ ݾ!
God! Keep the vibrator!
ȭ༭ .. ĵ.
Thanks for getting back to me... um... Candyman.
ĵ?
You're the Candyman?
׷.
Yes.
You're getting any exercise?
ϴ° ־?
?
Excuse me?
If you're not committed to personal fitness,
ǰ ƴϸ,
ɻ ſ .
I can't in good conscience sell to you.
ϸƴ ׷ ׶ѵ ݾƿ.
I wouldn't say Heylia is in the best shape.
ϸƴ ׺.
Heylia is a lazy fat-fat
׺ 索 պ ׾
ھ Ĵ°ſ.
and I'm hoping to put her in a diabetic coma so I have no problem selling to her.
ֿ?
Why?
Scare her.
ݰ ϴ°
Some people never learn until their life is on the line.
 ڱ λ ϴϱ.
You know what you are?
˾ƿ?
What am I?
?
.
Skinny-fat.
׷ װͿ ؼ  ؾߵǴ°?
And what are you gonna do about that?
츰  ϴ ſ.
We're gonna start exercising right away.
ƿ. ϴٰ.
Don't humor me. I'm very serious.
314Ŀ(142kg) .
I used to weigh 314 pounds.
! ؿ!
Wow! Congratulations!
ٽ
The key:
!
exercise.
װԿ, ° ƴϰŵ.
You know, I'm not buying for personal use.
Are your customers just a bunch of Fatty McFat-fats?
׷ ? ׺ΰ?
ַ ǿ ε
Well, they're smokers
ǿ ԰ԵǸ
but it stands to reason that if they
⵵ ϴϱ,
eat rather than smoke, they'll just be able to breath easier,
should they decide to exercise.
ϱ ϱⰡ .
װ ո̷α.
It's a reasonable assumption.
׸ å Ű ؼ
 ϵ ھ.
And I hope you'll take it upon yourself to encourage them to do so.
!
Of course!
׸ ִ° .
And I'll take everything you have.
׷?
Really?
.
Yeah.
׸?
And?
And I will make a greater effort to exercise.
׸ ϵ ؾ.
No, no.
ƴ, ƴϿ.
׸ Ҳ.
And I will exercise.
׷, װſ.
Yes, you will.
Ӱ ٽ Ʊ!
Great! Dumb and Dumber reunited.
! ٽ ݰ!
Man! It's good to see you!
.
You smell really good.
, Ӹ. ð .
You better get the fuck off me, dude. What's wrong with you?
? ƴ ڰ ٸ ߻ ƴ
Īϸ ȵǳ?
What? Can't a straight man admire the stink of another handsome straight man?
濡 ׷ .
Not unless you're in prison.
Գ?
Is that where you've been?
. ˷ī.
Close. Alaska.
ʴ ?  ¾?
What about you? What have you been up to?
ǳ Ȱ.
Same old, same old, dude.
Ȱ, ⸣...
Just dealing, growing,...
ʶ׽ ϰ.
doing a little pilates.
?
No!
I love that shit, man!
װ .
̿ Ű, , е 󸶳 µ.
Stretch you out, dude. Give you power, make you feel good as hell.
簡 ?
Hot instructor?
Ass like a peach, dude. You just wanna bite that shit.
̰ ְ , Ƹ ְ Ŵ.
! ..
Nice! Nice...
ܷ, Ⱦƾ?
So... Conrad, man, can you help me out with a little?
̰ û ׿?
It's a lot of weed, huh?
?
You got the money?
̸ŭ ȵǴµ...
For that much? I don't...
մԲ ɺθ µ ༭ ̴?
Great! Lady Saltine sends her little errand boy with no scratch.
?
Nancy?
׷, ħ ֹѰ ݸ ϰ ŵ.
Yes, she only paid for the half order she picked up this morning.
׸ ̰ ̴...
And that's the other half.
־ , .
You got my money, boy genius?
׷ϱ... ð ũ Ѵ ̰?
So huh... Nancy's getting pretty big, huh?
Ź.
Fucking kingpin.
̾?
What's so funny?
What? Oh... huh... Conrad does pilates.
? .. ׷ϱ.. ܷ尡 ʶ׽ Ѵݾƿ.
. ?
Okay. Where was I?
ߴ...
I'm surrounded...
鿡 Ѱž.
You're surrounded by the enemy.
The enemy edges in, closer... closer...
ٰ°, ...
, -  ġ°ž.
then when they're just inches away, you invoke the Dong-Hai defence.
װ ?
What's that?
You protect your dong, and you swing like your life depended on it.
⸦ ̷ ȣ ϸ鼭, ڻ ̷ ֵθ .
ִ!
Cool!
, !
I need to talk to you, you fucking perv!
Ҿ, .
All right, go practice that.
Ҹ ϴ°ž? ˷ī ģڰ ȭ߾?
What are you talking about? Did that loony chick from Alaska call?
ްϰ ϴ°ݾ.
No, I'm talking about what you did to Megan today.
ް ?
Who's Megan?
Megan! My girlfriend!
ް! ģ!
޽ ݾ.
Told her to take her clothes off when she IMd.
Oh that Megan!
.. ް!
׷, ؼ ׷ Ѱž, ؾ .
Yeah, I did that for you, bro'. You should be thanking me.
?
What?
ϴ.
That girl really digs you.
翬! ģݾ.
No shit! She's my fucking girlfriend.
¶ ѹ غ, ׷?
But you haven't got into her panties yet, have you?
Ű澵 ƴݾ!
That's none of your business!
װ ׷ ˾?
You know why?
װ ܰ ⸦ ϴ°ž.
'Cause you're afraid to make all the big moves
° ̶ ̾.
'cause she's all handicapped and shit.
װ װ .
But that's what you need to learn, buddy.
װ ¸ ٸ ϰ Ȱ ϸ
You gotta treat them like everybody else and then
ڿ ¶ ȸ ٴϱ.
it'll pop right open like a can of Pringles.
׷ϱ...
So...
׷ϱ, ´ غ ƾ. ո ȴٰ.
So, she's ready, man, you gotta go for it.
㿡 ?
You're gonna see her tonight?
- ׷.
- .. ׷..
- Yeah.
- Well...
϶, !
Silas, check me out!
Ʋ?
You better be right.
Ͼ.
Trust me, man.
ո .
It's good to go.
Hey Pants!
ȳ !
Ⱑ ´°ž?
Please tell me I didn't hear
15¥ ͸ӰŸ ϰ ̹ ߾?
that you had cyber sex with a 15-year-old deaf girl.
ƴ.
Absolutely not.
ù㿡 !
I want you out tonight.
?
Really?
ε.
'Cause you know I was just cooking dinner.
I want you out. Now!
! !
޴
Don't you wanna hear my menu
'cause I've got some really great recipes over
Ǹ 丮 µ ̾.
Ʊ ģ ܷ (Joint:ȭ).
at my friend Conrad's joint earlier today.
(ȭ) νƮ, ܵ ؽ(ؽ),
Pot roast, corned beef hash,
ῡ Ż
ϴµ (baked:а) Ƽ,
tonight though I'm gonna go italian with little baked ziti
and a big plate of spaghetti marijuana.
׸ ȭ İƼ ū ÷ ϳ .
̷ Ȱ ڽ!
You sneaky piece of shit!
Calm now, Nancy Pants!
, !
Isn't that the pot calling the kettle black.
ܿ ݰ ȭ?
Ѱž?
What did you do?
׵ Ϸ ģ ܷ带 ã .
Well, I went to my old friend Conrad to catch up on old times.
ܷ ?
You remember Conrad, don't you?
He's a pot dealer.
ȭ ݾ.
Ϸ ϸ ȭ ٷ ܷݾ.
He's the one you're supposed to call if you ever need a little puff.
׸ Ե, Ŀٶ ȭ ָ鼭
And much to my surprise, I was handed a giant bag of weed
and told it was for you.
ֶݾ.
?
Where's my stuff?
׷, ׷ "!
So, I thought "Wow!
ð ū ְų
Either Nancy's got a big problem
or Nancy's got a lot of friends."
ƴ ģ ڱ!"
׵ ģ ?
You've been making friends?
װ İ?
Where's my stuff?
, ־.
Don't worry, it's safe.
Don't worry? Everything you touch turns to shit.
? װ մ ߿ ȸѰ ݾ.
̶. سž.
I'm family. We'll work it out.
װ ھ.
I really want you to leave.
Look, the way I see it is
Ȳ ⿡
you're in way over your head here, you know.
ʹ ڽ Ȥϰ ִٰ,
, û鿡,
You've got a house, you've got bills,
׸ 븩, Ĵ° Ѱ ƴϾ.
you're a mommy, dealing is a fulltime job.
You need some help, Nancy Pants.
ڱ ʿ, .
Don't call me, Pants.
θ .
ִٰ ҷ, װ ƴϾ.
Judah called me Pants, not you.
׷, ׸, .
Yeah, I miss him too, Nancy.
 ϴ, ִٴ ̾,
Whatever you think about me, Judah was my brother.
߾.
And I loved him.
´ٰ.
And I have your back.
, 
.
Now, I'ma go inside and I'ma finish cooking dinner for the family.
I'm making stoned crabs.
.
̾, ϴ°ǵ,
ƿ ߰ŵ.
Sorry, I had to make that last one, I was working on them all the way home.
.
Hey.
You look hot in that leotard.
ϱ .
.
Take it off.
2?
Perv Jr?
̷ ʵ ݾ.
Come on you want to.
ε巯.
Your uncle was smoother.
̷.
I have cancer.
Transcript et synchro: Travis
- www.forom.com -